[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Adrenaline, or epinephrine, is one of the stress hormones our bodies produce. What is the effect of adrenaline on the human body?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It dilates pupils.", "It increases the blood sugar levels.", "It suppresses the immune system."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The soundtrack for which of these movies does not include the popular song Blue Moon, written by Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart?", "correct_answer": "Bitter Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Grease", "Blue Moon (2002)", "Notting Hill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is generally accepted that this was the first novel whose manuscript was typed on a typewriter.", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer", "incorrect_answers": ["The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", "The Great Gatsby", "Moby Dick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word tornado literally mean?", "correct_answer": "Thunderstorm", "incorrect_answers": ["Devil", "Death", "Danger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which film can you hear the following line? All right you proved your point. You broke into my vault. Congratulations, youre a dead man.", "correct_answer": "Oceans 11", "incorrect_answers": ["The Usual Suspects", "Oceans 13", "Oceans 12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Lamian Gardens of Rome are often claimed to be haunted by the ghost of the Roman Emperor Caligula, who died in what way?", "correct_answer": "Assassination", "incorrect_answers": ["Natural causes", "Suicide", "Poisoning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following flying vehicles entered the center of the Death Star and played the main part in destroying it in Star Wars Episode VI?", "correct_answer": "Millennium Falcon and X-Wing Fighter", "incorrect_answers": ["Y-Wing Fighter and X-Wing Fighter", "Millennium Falcon and A-Wing Fighter", "A-Wing Fighter and X-Wing Fighter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These organs are very sensitive and often fail in people with very high blood pressure or diabetes.", "correct_answer": "kidneys", "incorrect_answers": ["pancreas", "ovaries", "lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This concept was popularized in Dostoevskys Notes from the Underground, Pushkins Eugene Onegin and in many of the works of Turgenev.", "correct_answer": "The Superfluous Man", "incorrect_answers": ["The Super-Tribe", "The Total Man", "The Super Race"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Narcissus plants, commonly called daffodils, contain the toxin lycorine in which structure?", "correct_answer": "Bulb and leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Blossom", "Stamen", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "FAT, a file system developed by Microsoft, is the shortened form of what?", "correct_answer": "File Allocation Table", "incorrect_answers": ["File Accessible Table", "File Array Table", "File Acceptance Table"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas is based on the eponymous book, written by this famous counterculture author and journalist.", "correct_answer": "Hunter S. Thompson", "incorrect_answers": ["Cameron Crowe", "Lester Bangs", "Tom Wolfe"]}]